seeedstudio.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

This is the Privacy Policy of this website (the “Site”) and Seeed Technology Co., Ltd and/or its related parties which are the Site operator. As a part of normal operating procedures,

this website may collect, apply (under special circumstances) and discloses your information to third parties. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy, please do not continue.

Otherwise, you should have read, understood and agreed to be subject of this Privacy Policy, and be complied with all relevant laws and regulations.

Seeed Technology Co., Ltd retains the right to change, revise and renew this Privacy Policy without prior notice.

#### Personal Information

You can anonymous access to the Site and obtain information. We will explain the use of the information before requesting you to provide relevant information, and some sites of

the Site need your register to access. The Site will track some datum automatically in accordance with the user’s behavior. In order to provide better services, the Site use the datum

to make internal statistics, which including but not limited to the number of users and their interest or behavior. The Site collects the datum using Data Collection Device such as

“Cookies”. “Cookies” is a small file set on the user’s hard disk, helping the Site provide tailor-made services for the uses. And the Site provides some functions which are realization via

the “Cookies” only. The Site using the “Cookies” reduces the numbers of input password in a certain period.

#### The Use of Personal Information

You agree that the Site could use your information (including but not limited to the information in the files which are held by the Site and other information which are obtained from

currently and previously events on the Site) to resolve disputes, stop arguments, help to ensure that the transactions on the Site safety, and perform the obligations agreed with User

within this Site. Occasionally, the Site needs to identify problems or resolve disputes by investigating multiple users, even reviews the user’s information to identify which user holds

multiple ID. For limiting the fraud, illegal and criminal activities on the Site，you agree that the Site could check the your personal information either manually or with an automatic

program.

#### The Disclosure of Personal Information

The Site will protect the personal information via industry practice. Due to technical limitations, the Site cannot ensure that users of all private communications and other personal

information will not be disclosed by other sources not listed in the Privacy Policy. The Site has the obligation to provide personal information to the judicial organs and government

departments in accordance with the relevant laws and regulations.

#### Privacy Inquire

You have no right to request any user's private information during using contents on the Site or gathering information from it.

#### E-mail

You should not be allowed using the services or other e-mail forwarding services provided by the Site to send spam or to do something which would possible violate the laws and

regulations of the relative jurisdiction, social morality and the Site's User Agreement or Privacy Policy content. In addition to send e-mails, the Site will not use e-mail addresses for

any other purpose. The Site will not rent or sell these e-mail addresses. The Site will not store e-mail message or e-mail address permanently.

#### Responsibility

You should be responsible for your ID, passport, the registered e-mail address and all of other security settings. Therefore, the Site has no obligation to keep the above information.

#### Applicable Laws and Jurisdiction

Any controversy and dispute arising out of this website and this Privacy Policy shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the England and Wales and subject to the exclusive

jurisdiction of the England and Wales's court that has jurisdiction over the case.

#### The interpretation of this Privacy Policy is attributed to Seeed Technology Co., Ltd.
